And so this curve
now is something
that we understand and we
understand how to control it.
And if you go back to the
example of making glass tough,
I was just showing you these
ions, these sodium ions.
They're left in there.
Well, it turns out that you
can put ions into glass,
and maybe you're doing it
to change the viscosity
so the thing stays
liquid for longer,
and you can maybe work with
it in different regimes.
But maybe you're putting
the ions in there
to do something else.
And so actually there's
a whole another thing
you can do once you have ions
in the glass like sodium.
You can substitute them out.
Imagine that I
have-- that's what
this next picture is showing.
Imagine that I've
got a glass in here,
and those red
circles are sodium.
But now I've introduced a
different ion on the surface.
That's potassium.
What happens?
Well, if I have a high
concentration of potassium
and I put it on a
surface of glass that
has a bunch of
sodium in it, so now
I've got a glass with
sodium ions in it.
And I expose it to
a potassium bath.
So now I've got
potassium up here.
And what happens is if the
concentration is high enough
and the conditions are
right, I can get potassium
to go in for the sodium.
And so actually now
I can substitute.
So these were here.
I can now substitute
those for potassium.